<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<LanguageData>

    <!-- Psychic Sensitivity -->

    <PsychicSensitivityUpMajor.label>arcane mastery</PsychicSensitivityUpMajor.label>
    <PsychicSensitivityUpMajor.description>This weapon amplifies the wielder's magical aptitude by 40%. This only applies while the weapon is held.</PsychicSensitivityUpMajor.description>

    <PsychicSensitivityUpMinor.label>arcane expertise</PsychicSensitivityUpMinor.label>
    <PsychicSensitivityUpMinor.description>This weapon amplifies the wielder's magical aptitude by 20%. This only applies while the weapon is held.</PsychicSensitivityUpMinor.description>

    <PsychicSensitivityDownMinor.label>arcane dampener</PsychicSensitivityDownMinor.label>
    <PsychicSensitivityDownMinor.description>This weapon suppresses the wielder's magical aptitude by 15%. This only applies while the weapon is held.</PsychicSensitivityDownMinor.description>

    <PsychicSensitivityDownMajor.label>arcane fog</PsychicSensitivityDownMajor.label>
    <PsychicSensitivityDownMajor.description>This weapon suppresses the wielder's magical aptitude by 30%. This only applies while the weapon is held.</PsychicSensitivityDownMajor.description>

    <OnKill_PsyfocusGain.description>This weapon's persona focuses on deaths. If the weapon kills someone, the wielder will instantly gain 20% mana.</OnKill_PsyfocusGain.description>

    <OnKill_ThoughtGood.description>This weapon's persona loves to kill. If this weapon kills someone, its joy will emit a magical aura, making them happier for a few days.</OnKill_ThoughtGood.description>

    <OnKill_ThoughtBad.description>This weapon's persona hates killing. If this weapon kills someone, its sorrow will emit a magical aura, reducing their mood for a few days.</OnKill_ThoughtBad.description>

    <NeedKill.description>This weapon's persona find purpose in bloodshed. If it does not kill for 20 days, it will become angry and magically diminish the mood of whoever is bonded to it.</NeedKill.description>

    <PsyfocusMeditationBonus.label>arcane-meditative</PsyfocusMeditationBonus.label>
    <PsyfocusMeditationBonus.description>This weapon's persona is naturally meditative and helps improve it's its wielder connection to the background mana field while meditating. The wielder gains an extra 10% mana per day of meditation, as long as the weapon is held.</PsyfocusMeditationBonus.description>

    <NoPain.description>This weapon's persona is expert at channeling and absorbing the pain of it's weilder via it's extensive mana pathways. The one holding the weapon will feel no pain of any kind.</NoPain.description>

    <SpeedBoost.label>arcane speed</SpeedBoost.label>

    <HungerMaker.label>arcane hunger</HungerMaker.label>

    <NeuralHeatRecoveryGain.label>arcane load sink</NeuralHeatRecoveryGain.label>
    <NeuralHeatRecoveryGain.description>This weapon's persona has the ability to help dissipate the wielder's arcane load. The wielder's arcane load dissipation is improved by 0.15 per second.</NeuralHeatRecoveryGain.description>
</LanguageData>
