<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
		<VPE_WordofTrust.description>Speak to the prisoner while using manipulating their mind to reduce their resistance to recruitment. This spell can only reduce a prisoner's resistance, but cannot recruit them.</VPE_WordofTrust.description>
		<VPE_WordofProductivity.description>Using words of motivation with a heaping boost to metabolism, makes the touched target a more productive member of society for the next few days. Considered a hostile action and duration is affected by the target’s magical aptitude.</VPE_WordofProductivity.description>
		<VPE_BlindingPulse.description>Induce noise in the visual centers of the brain, obscuring vision of everyone near the target point. Lasts for half a minute, affected by magical aptitude.</VPE_BlindingPulse.description>
		<VPE_WordofAlliance.description>Speak words of friendship and benefits to a close target using mind control, helping them realize that you’re not all that bad. Only works on those willing to listen and effect scales with the caster's magical aptitude.</VPE_WordofAlliance.description>
		<VPE_GroupLink.description>Creates a sphere of mind domination magic around the caster, linking all pawns within to the caster and allowing any single target “Word of” spell to affect all others. The effect ends when those linked move out of range.</VPE_GroupLink.description>
		<VPE_WordofPain.description>Induces noise in the target’s pain centers of the brain and overstimulates their nerve endings, scaling with their magical aptitude.</VPE_WordofPain.description>
		<VPE_MindBreak.description>Magically lobotomizes the target and turns them into a serving, restless thrall. Very much unappreciated by their former factions.</VPE_MindBreak.description>
		<VPE_WordofProtection.description>Infuse the target’s body with mana making it more durable and resistant to damage. Lasts a long time and scales with the caster’s magical aptitude.</VPE_WordofProtection.description>
		<VPE_DrainPsyessence.label>drain mana</VPE_DrainPsyessence.label>
		<VPE_DrainPsyessence.description>Targeting a downed magically-talented pawn, harmonizes with their innate magical signature, copying it and repeating it back causing constructive magical field interference until the target's body is shaken apart from the immense magical resonance. The resulting pure resonant magical essence is bound to the caster, allowing them to learn, in a moment, what took the target their whole lifetime. The final moments of extreme destructive resonance will be felt by everyone for many kilometers around, causing diplomatic consequences with all factions.</VPE_DrainPsyessence.description>
		<VPE_MassHallucination.description>Creating a massive burst of mind domination magic, convincing nearby pawns that rooms are the absolute best they could possibly be. The resulting coma for the caster and the effect lasts for five days.</VPE_MassHallucination.description>
</LanguageData>
