<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<LanguageData>
    <Throne.description>A large, ornate chair designed for a dignity-focused mage to sit and meditate. Reigning on a throne is a form of meditation that builds up mana. For dignity mages, more impressive meditation thrones and thronerooms increase the rate of mana gain.</Throne.description>
    <GrandThrone.description>A massive, ornate chair, designed for dignity-focused mages to sit and meditate. Reigning on a throne is a form of meditation that builds up mana. For dignity mages, more impressive meditation thrones and thronerooms increase the rate of mana gain.</GrandThrone.description>

    <MeditationSpot.description>Designates a spot for meditation. Mages can meditate here to gain mana. If a focus object like a sculpture is nearby, the mage will be able to focus on it to boost their mana gain. However, different people are able to use different focus objects.</MeditationSpot.description>

    <NatureShrine_Small.description>A small shrine for honoring spiritual beings. Tribal mages can focus on this shrine while meditating to increase mana gain. Nature shrines lose their power if they are close to artificial structures, so they are always built in nature. Since they look like natural objects to unobservant outsiders, raiders will generally ignore them.</NatureShrine_Small.description>
    <NatureShrine_Large.description>A large shrine for honoring spiritual beings. Tribal mages can focus on this shrine while meditating to increase mana gain. Nature shrines lose their power if they are close to artificial structures, so they are always built in nature. Since they look like natural objects to unobservant outsiders, raiders will generally ignore them.</NatureShrine_Large.description>
    <AnimusStone.description>An ancient jade stone marked with sacred tribal carvings. Tribal mages can focus on these stones during meditation to increase their mana gain more than a typical nature shrine.\n\nDifferent tribal cultures tell different stories about these stones, but most agree that they were crafted by an ancient world spirit during a time of great power. Since they look like natural objects to unobservant outsiders, raiders will generally ignore them.</AnimusStone.description>
</LanguageData>
